NARDIN LACHOWSKI

full stack software developer

SUMMARY

Results oriented IT professional with over 5 years of experience in product integrations and implementation projects. Have worked at fast-paced internet and software companies where I developed strong organizational skills leading all phases of diverse technology initiatives. Recently earned my **certification** as a **full stack software developer** and I am eager to apply my knowledge to continue making a lasting impact in the field

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Technology Consultant - Implementations

Paytronix (Oct. 2019 - Present)

- · Manages and leads multifaceted implementation projects with varying product requirements.
- Translates client marketing requirements into rule-based technical solutions.
- Installs and configures POS software tailored to clients' program designs.
- Manipulates and handles migrations for large data sets in relational databases.
- Cross-functional collaborations with the engineering department on feature generation, requirements, and testing.
- Creates and maintains project documents and timelines.
- Regularly meets with Product teams to stay up to date on new features and to contribute ideas to roadmap.
- Communicates metrics and progress towards operational goals to internal business stakeholders.

Client Integration Engineer

CJ Affiliate (Dec. 2018 - Oct. 2019)

- Led engineering pre-sales efforts. Providing technical solutions and strategies during clients' onboarding journey.
- Worked closely with account managers to provide a seamless implementation process and successful deployment.
- API performance monitoring utilizing ELK Stack/ Kibana dashboards
- Drove technical discussions with clients' development teams.
- Communicated project delivery forecasts to leadership.
- QA of integrations prior to deployment on network.
- Provided post implementation support and continued program enhancements.
- Reviewed tracking trends for developing integration improvements.
- Identified business opportunities and developed strategic initiatives for ensuring customer retention.
- Contributed to in-app tracking solutions and global expansion initiatives.

Product Support Analyst

Indeed.com (Apr. 2015 - Dec. 2018)

- · Partnered closely with product managers during product launches and large scale bug investigations.
- · Liaised between business and technical leads to ensure product requests were resolved in a timely manner.
- Utilized SQL and other data tools to conduct thorough analysis of common trends to determine root cause, behavior, and impact.
- Thorough understanding of Google Tag Manager, Google Analytics, Google Apps and ability to manipulate G Suite products to produce functional entities.
- Stakeholder of the global Client Satisfaction and Peer-to-Peer feedback programs. Set forth reconstruction plan with Program Management in order to automate and enhance performance.
- Drove GDPR compliance initiatives with EMEA's Senior Directors.
- Supported third-party and ATS integrations and established strong, trusted relationships with business partners.
- Handled CRM administrative responsibilities for the Client Success department.

EDUCATION

University of Connecticut

Certificate Full Stack Dev - 2021

B.S. in Biological Sciences - 2013

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Programming languages:

JavaScript, React.js, Python, Node.js

Web Development:

HTML, CSS, jQuery, Redux, Express.js, Bootstrap, Materialize, Material UI

Database and Analytics:

SQL, MongoDB, MySQL, JSON, AJAX, RESTful APIs, XML, Google Tag Manager

Tools and Technologies:

Heroku, Git, ELK Stack, Miro, JIRA, Confluence, Salesforce, Zendesk, Smartsheets, ELK Stack, User Auth

Additional Skills:

Deployment | Project Management | Employee onboarding and mentoring | Agile methodology | Cross-functional Collaboration | Customer Service | Product Research